make4fun.com 2014-04-24

# Privacy Policy - Avzio

## **Make4fun Privacy Notice**

## ****

**** Last updated: November 21, 2008

The use, access, or download of the Make4fun website(s) and/or Make4fun software and any Make4fun services and products (collectively, "Make4fun") provided by AVSOFT CORP. are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments or updates hereto, which is to demonstrate Avnex's firm commitment to your privacy and privacy-related concerns.

**Personal Information Collection  
**

  * **Non-Account Activity.** You can read, view, watch, listen, comment and download stories, images, audios, videos or other content (collectively, "content") on Make4fun without having a Make4fun Account. You can also contact us about a particular content without having a Make4fun Account. 
  * **Account-Related Activity.** Certain other activities on Make4fun-like uploading content, flagging favorite content, getting Freekey of products, retrieving your licenses of products, posting and replying to topics at Make4fun forums-require you to have a Make4fun Account. 

We ask for some personal information when you create a Make4fun Account, including your full name, your email address, your date of birth, an account name (or user ID), and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A Make4fun Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.

We do not collect personal information-like contact information, work information, education info-about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntarily basis; like (i) provide Make4fun with information in connection with account registration, or (ii) update your profile information after registration at Make4fun.

  * **Non-Personally Identifiable Information and Usage Information.** We may record information specifically related to the use of a particular Make4fun feature or about your usage, like when you use Make4fun, the frequency of Make4fun access, the content you access, the favorite content you flag, as well as information you display or click on in Make4fun (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any content posted at the direction of users onto the Make4fun website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.
  * **Personal Disclosure.** Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online (on comments, forum topics, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available.

**A Special Note about Children and Parents**

Our site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we are committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). On those areas of the sites that ask for age, we do not collect personal information from individuals who identify themselves as under the age of 13, except in limited circumstances where we believe that such collection is permitted under COPPA

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail, as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13.

**Information publicity**

  * Information about you from your Make4fun account registration (except for your email address and full name) and your account activity will be provided to other Users of Make4fun. This includes the date you opened your account, the date you last logged into your account, the content you have uploaded, your date of birth, and your country.
  * You can add further information about yourself that will visible to other Users on your profile page. This includes a profile picture, gender, creative skills, contact information, personal hobbies, education background, work information, social information. You can always choose to make these information (except your profile picture and your gender) public or private.
  * Your account name (not your email address nor your full name) is displayed to other Users when you engage in certain activity on the site, such as you upload content or comment content or send messages through Make4fun. Other Users can contact you through messages and comments.
  * Your uploaded content list will be visible to other Users on your Make4fun account's upload page.
  * Any content that you submit to Make4fun may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * Any personal information that is voluntarily disclosed online on messages to other Users, comments to content, Make4fun's forum topics, or in classified areas within Make4fun becomes public information.

Our use of your information

  * Your account name (not your email address nor your full name) is displayed to other Users when you upload content, make comments for content or send messages through Make4fun and other Users can contact you through messages and comments.
  * Your personal information will be used to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of Make4fun, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.
  * Any content that you submit to Make4fun may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to statistically analyze Make4fun usage, to improve the quality and design of Make4fun and to create new content, features, functions, products, promotions, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.
  * We internally use your personal information to occasionally contact you by email to notify you our special offers of our products. If you do not wish to receive these emails, you can always let us know by clicking the **Unsubscribe** link at the end of the emails you received, and we will happily abide by your wishes.
  * We use your email address and, in rare situations your mailing address or phone number, without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes from time to time (such as notifying you of major Make4fun changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We use cookies, and log file information to: (i) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Make4fun; (ii) provide custom, personalized content and information; (iii) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (iv) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (v) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, and contests (if any).

**Cookies**

Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the use of cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of Make4fun including to operate and improve offerings through the Website; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Website; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you.

Make4fun does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of Make4fun may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies.

**Modification of Personal Information**

All your personal information, except for Username (your user ID), your full name and your email address, can be changed using the edit link of the appropriate part in your profile. Please note that changing of your personal information from Make4fun's database will not prevent Make4fun from using gathered anonymous information.

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

Make4fun allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within Make4fun. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Make4fun. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Make4fun does not provide any User's personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks. Make4fun does, however, perform statistical analysis of User usage in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various parts of Make4fun, and we shares that information with current and prospective advertisers, and other interested third parties. But, this information is aggregated data only (statistics, etc.), and contains no personally identifiable information whatsoever. 

Please note that if an advertiser asks Make4fun to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of Make4fun, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. Make4fun's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Make4fun is maintained and dealt with by Make4fun in accordance with this privacy policy.

Any personal information that is voluntarily disclosed online in comments to Make4fun content, in Make4fun's forum topics, or in classified public areas within Make4fun becomes public information and might be collected and disseminated by third-parties, and result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third-parties. The disclosed information in such cases becomes public information and this third-party conduct is out of the control of Make4fun. 

Make4fun also contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

**Binding Agreement**

The use, access, or download of the Make4fun is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions. By using Make4fun, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the top of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of Make4fun following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**Contact Information**

Please address comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy to us via email to: **[makeforfun@make4fun.com](mailto:makeforfun@make4fun.com) **
